- ConversationTopicId: 12A_Don
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Don_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_Don_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12A_Shae
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Shae_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_Shae_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12A_Shazaan
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Shazaan_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_Shazaan_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12A_Tomira
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Tomira_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_Tomira_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12A_Chandu
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_Chandu_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_Chandu_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_TalkLochnir
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_TalkLochnir_new_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_MSQ_06_ToMiclot_TalkLochnir_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_TalkMoira
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_TalkMoira_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_MSQ_10_ConfrontLochnir_TalkMoira_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12_03_MSQ_10_Lochnir_Explains
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_10_Lochnir_Explains_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_MSQ_10_Lochnir_Explains_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: 12A_LochnirTalk01
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12_02_MSQ_12_SerPayneBennett
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_TalkTo_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_MSQ_12_CampTutorial_TalkTo_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: 12A_PayneTalk02
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12_12_MSQ_15_GraceOMalleyPre
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_TalkGracePre_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_TalkGracePre_a"
  AchievementUnlock: 12A_Grace15A
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12_11_MSQ_15_GraceOMalley
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_TalkTo_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_MSQ_15_DefeatNavigator_TalkTo_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: 12A_Grace15
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_TalkMoira
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_TalkTo_Prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_TalkTo_Response_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_TalkLochnir
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_TalkLochnir_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_MSQ_17_LochnirsNotes_TalkLochnir_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12A_MSQ_19_RegentJinJae
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_TalkTo_Prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_MSQ_19_MeetPercilla_TalkTo_Response_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_TalkRegent
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_TalkRegent_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_MSQ_21_FindGrace_TalkRegent_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12_01_MSQ_04_SerPayneBennett
  PlayerPrompt: "@12A_MSQ_04_TalktoPayne_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12A_MSQ_04_TalktoPayne_a"
  AchievementUnlock: 12A_PayneTalk01
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1225_Giacomo_HousingGeneral
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_Giacomo_HousingGeneral_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1225_Giacomo_HousingGeneral_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: S_downpayment
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1225_Giacomo_HousingStorage
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_Giacomo_HousingStorage_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1225_Giacomo_HousingStorage_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: 12_Quest_Housing_3b
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 1225_Giacomo_HousingTrophy
  PlayerPrompt: "@1225_Giacomo_HousingTrophy_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@1225_Giacomo_HousingTrophy_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: 12_Quest_Housing_6
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
